Okay, welcome to Brought to You by Broughtcast News for Wednesday, February 11th, 2016.
Mike Adams, thank you for joining me here today.
As always, we have a lot to cover and it's an interesting mix of some good news.
We have some good news coming out of the EPA on deregulation.
We've got some bad news about Netanyahu is now in DC, probably showing Trump the last
blackmail card that he has on him to say you have to attack Iran.
And today I've interviewed former CIA counterterrorism case officer, John Kiriakou.
And it's a fantastic interview.
I'm going to play about half of it today and half of it tomorrow.
So about 30 minutes of that interview coming up here later today.
And it's all about Iran.
Well, I mean, it starts with Iran, but you know, it when you start to talk about Iran,
you eventually you have to talk about China.
You have to talk about energy.
You have to talk about Russia.
You have to talk about rare earths.
You have to talk about US military readiness.
You have to talk about Iran's anti ship missile capability.
You have to talk about Israel.
You have to talk about Netanyahu.
I mean, one thing leads to another.
So it's a really great conversation.
And one of the things I love about John Kiriakou is that he's so intelligent.
He's so well informed.
And the reason I invited him is because I also sense his humanity.
Now in case you don't know who John Kiriakou is.
He's the guy that blew the whistle on the CIA's illegal torture campaign.
This was many years ago under Obama and they charged him, you know, the Obama administration
retaliated against him and charged him with multiple felony crimes involving of course
the handling of classified information.
So in other words, if the government is doing something crazy illegal and unconstitutional
but classified and if you blow the whistle on that, then they charge you with
the crime while they continue to get away with all the torture.
Sounds kind of like what's happening with the Epstein situation right now, right?
Total cover up of the whole Epstein blackmail network, the child trafficking, the child rape,
the child freaking cannibalism going on, or at least it went on according to the emails,
completely covered up by Trump and Pam Bondi and the FBI, etc.
Well, John Kiriakou blew the whistle on the torture program years ago.
And so they convicted him.
I mean, well, actually, I think he took a plea deal and he was sent to prison.
And so he served time in prison.
And when he got out, he kept his humanity intact.
He kept his integrity.
And you know, look, you may or may not agree with John Kiriakou on whatever politics
at this point, it doesn't matter.
It really doesn't matter.
I don't care if somebody is on the left or on the right.
I don't care if they're a Christian or Muslim or Jew or a Hindu or a Sikh or a Buddhist.
None of that matters.
You know what matters to me?
And I hope you too, I think so, is whether we operate with pro-human principles.
If I can find people who operate with pro-human principles, who have compassion, who are
pro-life in the greater sense of the term that is, you know, let's stop the genocide.
Let's stop the senseless killing.
Let's stop the senseless wars.
Let's stop the torture.
Let's, you know, all this.
If we can find people who are on the side of humanity and ultimately the side of truth
and love, we should celebrate those people.
And I like to talk to those people.
So that's what this is about today.
John Kiriakou, I think, I think an extraordinary American.
And you'll find that actually many of the people that I interview are people who have
been imprisoned.
Why?
Because they have integrity.
Because they refuse to buckle.
They refuse to take a deal.
Now, you know, compare that with somebody like Dan Bongino.
Dan Bongino saw all the crimes, right?
He was, what was he, deputy director of the FBI, I think?
So recently he resigned and he had no one prosecuted.
He covered up for the pedos.
He won't even name them publicly.
So because people like Dan Bongino, because he's willing to cover for the pedophiles and
the child rapists and the child traffickers, he gets offered a job at Fox News, you see.
Whereas someone who tells the truth, like John Kiriakou, gets sent to prison.
That's the difference.
And that's why I much prefer to talk to whistleblowers who serve time in prison rather than sellouts
who work for Fox News.
Just saying, you know, Dan Bongino is, in my opinion, he's a disgrace to this nation.
And you know, I don't go out of my way to attack individuals just for the fun of it.
For me to name somebody, they have to have earned it.
And you know, it's rare that I name specific people who I see as doing evil things or being
deeply involved in corruption or, or, or just failing to do their jobs.
I mean, for God's sake, Dan Bongino went to Washington.
He was there to clean up the place along with Cache Patel, along with Trump for that
matter, drain the swamp, lock her up, build the wall.
Remember that?
Yeah, it's all been completely abandoned.
And Bongino went right along with it.
So you know, he deserves every bit of criticism that we could level against him.
And you know, Fox News had to bail him out because his podcast is obviously a total catastrophe.
Nobody wants to hear Dan Bongino scream at them and call them, you know, total idiots
because they don't understand how hard it was for him to cover up for pedophiles
in Washington, DC.
You know, what a disgrace.
Anyway, I've got that interview coming up for you here today.
I don't think Dan Bongino will ever be on my show, but that's okay.
That's okay.
I've got a special report about the Ring doorbell and why it's a surveillance device that people
are installing on their own homes.
And the reason I even bring it up is because Ring had apparently a Super Bowl ad.
I saw some clips of it.
I didn't watch the Super Bowl, but the ad has been circulating and the ad pretends
that Ring doorbells or Ring video doorbells are so useful because they can help you
find your lost dog.
Yeah, that's just the cover story.
It's really a human surveillance network and you know, law enforcement can tap into it,
the NSA, the CIA, whatever they can all tap into it.
And because of so-called anti-terrorism laws and the Patriot Act and everything, they
don't even need a warrant.
All they do is they contact, you know, the Ring doorbell companies like, hey, just
give us all the video footage from this address.
You think Ring says no?
No, not a chance.
They turn it over.
So anyway, I have a whole report about that.
And why is it that so many people are so stupid that they will literally install a surveillance
device on their own home to watch them enter and leave their own home?
That's crazy.
So I've also got a special report on Netanyahu invoking what I call his final blackmail
gambit on Trump.
That's what's going on right now.
Not the reason Netanyahu had to fly to the United States because he had to threaten Trump
to his face and remind Trump what will happen if Trump doesn't follow orders from the real
president of the United States, which is Netanyahu.
Netanyahu, of course, has all the piles of blackmail on not just Trump, but everybody
in the Trump administration and probably his family members, et cetera, who are deeply
involved in all kinds of crypto scams, it turns out.
Do you know that most of the, well, they're called shitcoins in the industry.
The shitcoins launched by Trump's family members have all plummeted like 95 to 99 percent
since they were launched roughly a little over a year ago.
It's just a giant rug pull, just a total scam.
And they can be prosecuted for some of the things they've done.
And I believe the insider trading, how many times has Trump whipsawed the tariff situation
creating huge, huge profits for people who had insider knowledge about industries, everything
from copper to oil, to manufacturing industries, what have you.
Now, speaking of tariffs, it looks like the Supreme Court is set to rule against
Trump's tariffs because, of course, what Trump is doing is blatantly unconstitutional
and illegal.
Every honest person already realizes that the Supreme Court's going to rule against
Trump, and that's going to cause the United States government to have to send back
all the billions of dollars that it's collected from companies that paid all these tariffs,
which ended up raising consumer prices on everything.
Tariffs really ultimately end up being a tax on the American people, even though Trump
is always bragging about how much money he's raised on the tariffs, that's bragging about
raising taxes on the people.
So the Supreme Court is likely to rule that the tariffs are
illegal. And that's actually going to be great for America. The best way to have a golden age
in America is to reverse Trump's economic policies, because they are catastrophic for small businesses,
for importers, for retailers, and for the economy as a whole. They're catastrophic for
manufacturers in America as well, because manufacturers depend on imports from many
other nations. In addition, the tariffs have been used as a bludgeon weapon to punish our allies,
countries like India or Japan or even South Korea and Taiwan and other countries. And that's made
enemies out of friends. Well, I mean, perhaps you can't say enemies, but it's created animosity
among allies who should be strong allies. And now, they don't trust America that much,
especially under Trump. And I think a lot of countries around the world can't wait for Trump
to be shown the exit, which could happen if things go badly in this attack on Iran. This could be
the end of the Trump administration, which I think more and more people across America are
actually praying for the Trump regime to end, because it has been so catastrophic in so many
ways, the total violation of the civil rights of Americans by the ICE thugs, the blatant murder,
the execution of Americans on the streets by the ICE thugs, the tariffs I already mentioned,
and then the wars. And the total sellout to Zionism, where the entire Trump administration
completely betrays his own base, he threw MAGA under the bus in order to appease a war criminal.
Netanyahu is one of the worst war criminals in the history of our world who Trump invites like a
friend to the White House while Trump ignores what's happening to his own support base in
terms of economic losses, losses of freedom of speech, losses of civil liberties and job
losses, and so on. So we are living in a country, those of you who are Americans, we're living in
a country with a crumbling infrastructure. The railroads are crumbling, the bridges, the roads,
the ports, the refineries, everything's crumbling. Technology, military, education, it's all
crumbling. While the money is being sent to carry out war crimes and genocides, civilians
mostly, women and children, and doctors and food aid workers. And while the entire federal government
is compromised by a pedophile blackmail, because apparently the vast majority of the people who
run this country are satanic pedophiles who eat children from time to time. I'm not saying that
they do it every day. It's not like they're carry out lunch, but they eat children. That's
now clear. Every time they say jerky, that's what that means. And they are all invested in violence
and genocide and war and death and suffering and economic collapse. And that's not what MAGA
was supposed to stand for, obviously. MAGA was supposed to make America great again.
Instead, it's been total destruction of America and a total sellout and basically
straight up betraying America for the interests of a foreign master who represents
Satan. I mean, that's really where we are in the world right now. Now, I'm going to shift gears
here. There's something else happening that's a very big deal in economics. You're about to see
a major revision in the Bureau of Labor Statistics, what it calls its annual benchmark
revision, which revises the jobs numbers. And this is anticipated to be a massive revision.
Now, this revision is necessary because much of what the government has been reporting over the
last couple of years in terms of jobs has been completely fake, just totally fake. And this
is the way the federal government works today. It also worked this way under Biden,
where they published these amazing employment numbers and job growth and job creation.
And then a couple of quarters later, they go back and revise those back to zero.
But by that time, you know, the stock market has gone up because everybody says the economy
is booming. And right now, Trump is carrying on the same, you know, tradition of economic
bullshit that Joe Biden carried on, which is just claiming everything's great. This is a golden
age. The economy is booming. It's stronger than ever. Well, except they're about to delete
almost a million jobs from the official numbers, jobs that never existed.
Goldman estimates that the number, the revision number could be anywhere from 750,000 to 900,000
jobs. And Fed Governor Christopher Waller has said, this was published online, he said, quote,
last year's data will be revised downward soon to likely show that there was virtually no growth
in payroll employment in 2025, zero zip nada. Yeah, no growth. So the first year of Trump's
presidency actually had zero growth in payroll, zero. Unlike the numbers that we've been
being told by the White House press secretary, you know, the professional
liars and spin doctors. So as Trump always does, when he sees numbers that he doesn't like, he'll
just say they're fake. Actually, this is a correction of fake numbers. This is bringing it back from
what was fake to reality. But Trump will say that they're rigged, as he always does. And he'll
say, oh, the BLS is trying to make me look bad. But see, Trump's living in a delusional
fairy tale land. Obviously, you know, so many examples of this, where Trump is saying things
are awesome, while people are unemployed, people are being replaced by AI, losing their jobs,
food prices are going up continually, like crazy, while Trump says there's zero inflation.
So you know, Trump Trump is just forever, just feeding us a line of complete bullshit
about the economy, sorry about the profanity. There's just, there's no other
term to describe precisely what's happening here. You know, we're in the era of Trump's
imaginary economy. You know, I did a song about that last year called The Economy in Your Head
that people really enjoyed. Oh, speaking of songs, I've got the new music video almost ready for
you here of my new song, The Great Cratering. And that should be out. I think we're just
putting in the captions right now. That should be out probably by tomorrow. So I'll include it as
soon as we have it. In any case, the employment numbers are about to be revised in a horrible way.
This is probably going to hammer the stock market today. So, and again, I'm recording this right
around midnight, long before the market opens. But I'm guessing that the market's going to
be hammered pretty hard. And remember that AI tools are also becoming so capable and compelling
that many of the tech companies are no longer necessary because people can just use AI to
write their own software. They don't need to license software as a service or SaaS, S-A-A-S.
The whole SaaS market is on the rocks right now or on the brink, you could say, because a lot of SaaS
products that have been very lucrative over decades are now completely obsolete because of new AI
tools like Claude Code or Claude Opus 4.6, which I've been using for several days. In fact, I'm
watching it right now. It's running Bash commands in my console right now, fixing some bugs.
And it's amazing. It's amazing. I can tell it to create a photoshop clone. Write a program that
lets me edit graphics or write a program that lets me edit audio or write a program that translates
this video into a transcription text, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera. It will do everything I need
or write a calendar program if people still want those things. I don't know why everybody's
so intrigued by their calendars. That's just so funny. But whatever you want to write, it will
write it. My calendar is always the same, like finish up everything I can so I can vibe code for
the rest of the day. That's my calendar. Unfortunately, my schedule has been pretty busy.
So anyway, get ready for some pretty, pretty crazy updates to the jobs numbers and some
volatility. Probably gold and silver will go higher based on this, I would imagine. But we'll see.
All right. So I promised I was going to share some good news with you about the EPA and the
deregulation under Lee Zeldin. So I'm going to play that report for you next. Here we go.
So according to numerous news reports, including the Wall Street Journal, the EPA is finally
about to revoke the 2009 so-called Endangerment Finding. And this is under EPA director Lee Zeldin,
who is one of the few administration officials that I've overall been pretty happy with,
because he stopped all these fraudulent grants that the EPA
EPA was sending out, which is just money laundering anyway, and now he's going to stop this Endangerment
finding.
Now, the Endangerment finding has been the pillar of all these laws of restricting combustion
engine emissions and cracking down on the energy use and demanding these insane impossible
miles per gallon efficiencies from automakers and things like that.
The Endangerment finding is essentially the foundation for federal greenhouse gas regulation.
And the finding had claimed this whole time that CO2, which is plant fertilizer, it's plant
food in the air, that these gases, quote, threaten the public health and welfare of current
and future generations.
And thus from that Endangerment finding alone, the EPA gave itself a massive amount of new
power without any laws, without congressional approval, without voter approval.
It gave itself new powers, and this was under Obama of course, to basically terrorize America's
businesses and to shut down economic productivity and calling it, you know, saving the planet.
But of course, CO2 was never a threat to humanity.
CO2 is necessary to grow crops.
CO2 is necessary for rain forests to flourish.
CO2 obviously is part of photosynthesis.
You can't have plants without CO2 in the air, and we barely have any CO2.
It's just slightly over 400 parts per million in the atmosphere, and plants are starving
for it.
In fact, as CO2 levels have slowly risen over the last few decades, it's caused the re-greening
of many areas of Earth that were either deserts or semi-arid areas that are now becoming
grasslands or light forests.
And this has been proven out by NASA photos over the decades.
I think since 1975, these photos have shown the greening of Earth.
So the more CO2 that's in the atmosphere, the greener Earth becomes.
Even though the climate cultists who don't understand anything about science, they claim
that CO2 is bad for the planet, and somehow they even claim that carbon dioxide is bad
for plants, which is crazy.
And this is what led them to these insane schemes that even, I think Bill Gates was
involved in some of these where they would purchase millions of acres of forest,
and they would cut down all the trees and bury them, claiming they were saving the planet.
So only in the lunatic minds of climate cultists could you kill millions of trees and claim
you're saving the planet, because that's insane, right?
That's completely insane.
And also, basic science, obviously, says that carbon dioxide is necessary for food
crop production.
It's necessary for pollination plants everywhere.
If you want to have pollinators, you know, honeybees and bumblebees and whatever pollinates,
you better have plants with flowers.
And higher levels of CO2 allow more flowering.
And did you also know that higher levels of CO2 produce more nutrients in food crops?
That's right.
Look it up.
You can find the proof of that yourself if you want to.
So low levels of CO2 starve the crops and end up starving humanity.
In fact, the entire climate change cult and hoax, it is a giant hoax, is really part of
a global depopulation agenda to create food scarcity and starve the planet and also deprive
Western civilization of energy.
And we now are paying a steep price for that as China is winning the AI race, the race to
superintelligence, which depends on affordable power to power the data centers where the AI
development is taking place.
That's why China is winning with these breakthrough models like DeepSeek and Quinn and Kimmy
K2 and others.
China is winning.
While the West, what do we have in America?
The entire Eastern power grid is totally tapped out.
You can't add any more data centers to it.
We've hit the limit.
And why?
Why do we have a limit like that?
Because of Obama and Biden and the climate cultism that said energy is bad and we can't
use energy.
We can't burn natural gas.
We can't have coal-fired power plants.
They were even opposed to nuclear power, which doesn't even emit CO2.
It's crazy.
They said we have to have just wind turbines and solar, which I agree wind turbines and
solar can definitely assist.
But since we still don't have good battery technology for grid shifting, wind and solar
alone can't power a modern technological society because you need data centers to run at night
and when it's raining and when it's cloudy.
And again, when it's night because it turns out that night happens every night.
I mean, imagine that.
The climate lunatics still have never figured that out.
They think that the sun is shining 24 seven everywhere on the planet, which isn't possible.
So the EPA is going to yank this, this foundational declaration, which was always junk science
to begin with.
So Lee Zeldin said, quote, this amounts to the largest act of deregulation in the
history of the United States.
Interesting, huh?
And this will end the climate crisis fraud.
And you notice that every crisis that we've lived through for the last few decades has been
fake like COVID-19 totally engineered fake pandemic, right?
And the climate crisis completely fake, totally made up by Al Gore and others.
It was a globalist agenda, ultimately trying to achieve the same thing as the COVID-19
pandemic, which was depopulation, get people to take the jabs, get people to stop
using energy, get people to starve because the farms can't produce as much food, you know,
dim the sky, block the sun is stratospheric aerosol injection.
They're literally trying to block the sun, which is something that maybe Satanists would
want to do, you know, but, but not normal people who want life to exist on this planet.
I mean, you, you'd have to be like cosmically evil to think that blocking the sun would
be good for the plants on earth.
When plants need photosynthesis, obviously, but this is what again, this is what radical
leftists and climate cultists believe and it just shows you that their beliefs are rooted
in wildly irrational, highly destructive fake belief systems.
But you know those fake belief systems permeated the entire scientific community since 2009.
And if you ran a science lab at a university or, you know, you have a couple of graduate
students and you're running some kind of project, the only way that you ever got grant money
is if you claim to be working on some project that would prove that climate change was
real.
I mean, there are grants in other areas, obviously, you know, optics or whatever,
but if you were dealing with the area of atmospheric science or agriculture or anything
related to climate, you had to conclude that climate change was real and that it was urgent
and that it was a crisis and then you would get government grant money from the NIH or
other providers.
So it was a science laundering scheme.
They'd laundered the fake science to make money to pay themselves so they could keep
on producing fake science that the government wanted.
So the government was basically buying fake science the way a DC politician would buy a
cheap hooker.
They were just buying what they wanted and so therefore it didn't resemble science at all.
It wasn't science, it was all theater this entire time.
So Interior Secretary Doug Burgum said in an interview recently, he said, quote, more
energy drives human flourishing.
He's right.
He continues, energy abundance is the thing that we have to focus on, not regulating certain
forms of energy out.
Yeah, he's correct.
He's correct.
If you don't have abundant, affordable energy, you don't have a civilization that's moving
forward and you will lose the AI wars, 100 percent, and you will lose in terms
of industrial output or industrial competitiveness.
If you wonder why can China manufacture so many things so much more affordably than the
United States and especially more affordably than Western Europe, it's because China has
lower energy costs and also lower labor costs and fewer environmental restrictions.
But energy costs are the biggest part of that equation.
And in Europe right now, most of Western Europe energy costs are through the roof.
And on the east coast of the United States, you've got electricity costs that are
as high as in some places, like 35 cents a kilowatt hour.
And I think in Hawaii, it's very high there as well.
In China, it can be a fraction of that.
It can be five cents a kilowatt hour in some areas or certainly under 10 in most
areas of China.
So China can produce AI cognition at a fraction of the price of the United
States, and that matters.
That matters for competitiveness.
that matters for the race to superintelligence, which also, ultimately, that means that's
the race for new science because almost all of the new science in the years ahead is going
to be conducted by AI, not by humans.
Humans won't be doing the research.
The research will be done by AI burning tokens and burning electricity.
So if you don't have electricity, you can't really do much science.
Seriously, that's where this is all going.
It's already happening.
Okay?
This is actually good news for America.
We need to unleash the energy infrastructure of this country.
And right now, yeah, that means pipelines.
It means natural gas, which is abundant in North America.
And it means oil, which is also abundant in and around North America.
However, the longer term shift is clearly going to go to either coal fusion or hot fusion
or much greater efficiencies in things like solar panels combined with advances in battery
technology that are no longer just theoretical.
They're very real.
Two companies out of China right now, BYD and CATL, CATL, they have just announced breakthrough
battery technology using sodium ion chemistry.
CATL uses that.
Plus, of course, they have lithium ion chemistry, lithium iron phosphate typically.
But BYD, I think, just announced a sodium sulfide battery chemistry.
If I'm getting that right, I'm going to have to dig into that one a little bit more to find
out what they're doing.
The thing is, these batteries can cycle now tens of thousands of times, which makes
them perfect for daily use to shift solar panel energy into these batteries during
the daylight hours and then have the batteries draw down at night and then have it
cycle every day as the sun comes up and goes down, et cetera.
Now, lithium was horrible for that because it could only handle a couple thousand cycles
and then you would lose much of the capacity.
Also, lithium lost lots of efficiencies in extreme cold weather, whereas this new
battery technology functions very well across a broad spectrum of temperatures and it also
doesn't have runaway thermal events, i.e., my batteries blew up, giant fire that
nobody can put out, things like that.
In addition, the new battery chemistry is a fraction of the price, like 10% of the
price of what lithium ion was just two years ago.
So what this means is that suddenly solar and wind also become much more viable
because of the battery technology, but Trump has tariffs on China.
So we can't get the batteries from China.
We can't even buy the EVs made in China, even though they're the best cars
in the world now, by far.
China has the best vehicles in the world.
Blows away Tesla, blows away Ford, blows away everything made in America or
Europe, blows away, you know, Saab and Volvo and everything else that you can
think of.
Volkswagen, right?
Blows it all away.
But you're not allowed to buy them because the American people are being
cut off from Chinese technology, including Chinese battery technology.
That's on purpose.
It's to force America to use more fossil fuels because it's the natural
gas people and the oil people that donate strongly to the Trump campaign,
you see, or, you know, the GOP in general.
So they want America addicted to hydrocarbons.
And I agree that we need to use hydrocarbons right now, but we also need
to expand the infrastructure to non-hydrocarbon energy sources.
And that means being able to acquire advanced battery technology from China.
Now we tried to build those batteries in America.
There was a company called Natron that was going to build sodium ion
batteries.
I think they were out of Minnesota and they had a factory that was in,
I think, Atlanta, that it was supposed to be a $1.5 billion
factory.
Yeah, they went bankrupt six months ago or whatever it was.
So we don't make any batteries in America that are the new chemistry
or breakthrough sodium ion or anything like that.
We got to get them from China or maybe South Korea.
But South Korea is kind of behind China.
Nevertheless, if we don't start bringing in battery technology,
we're never going to be able to grow our energy infrastructure.
So hopefully the EPA recognizes this.
And there's one more factor in all this that's really critical,
which is that America has all these economic sanctions against Russia.
And the upshot of that is that we haven't been able to get the gas
turbines that turned natural gas into electricity.
You run a giant turbine generator.
That's how you can power the grid with sometimes 300 megawatts
or one gigawatt of energy.
It's a giant gas turbine.
Well, Russia makes the best gas turbines, or at least they're up
there in the top two or three.
But we can't buy them because we have economic sanctions against
Russia.
So there's a long wait time like years.
I've covered this before.
It's five to 10 years wait time to get gas turbines.
So even if you have natural gas in America, you can't turn it
into electricity because you don't have the turbines.
And the wait time is years, like I just said.
So you can't just take gas out of the ground
and just pump it into the electric wires.
It doesn't work that way.
You have to rotate a coil of copper
in order to have alternating current.
That's how generators work.
And if you can't rotate it, you got nothing.
So all the oil in the world isn't useful
unless you have a generator that burns the oil,
or all the gas in the world isn't
useful unless you have gas turbines, et cetera.
And all the solar is not that useful
unless you have batteries.
So it's these intermediary technologies that are missing.
It's the missing link to America's energy abundance.
And you know what the missing link really is all about?
It's about the fact that Trump has become isolationist
and has cut off America from China and Russia.
Because again, Russia provides the turbines,
China provides the batteries.
If we were engaged in trade with Russia and China,
our domestic energy infrastructure
would be much stronger, much more abundant,
and electricity prices would be plummeting.
And the average American voter
would be able to afford to buy groceries more
because they wouldn't have to pay a double or triple
power bill, which is what's happening to many of them
right now, especially during the colder months.
So if you're wondering why your electricity costs so much,
it's because of Trump's tariffs
and Joe Biden's economic sanctions against Russia,
but Trump's trade war with China is continuing this.
That's why.
We need gas turbines.
We need batteries.
If we have those, we've already got plenty of sunlight
and we can get solar panels from India or Japan
if we have, or South Korea, we can get solar panels.
They don't have to come from China.
We've got plenty of sunlight.
We've got plenty of deserts.
We could cover the deserts with solar panels
or it wouldn't even need to.
Just a small portion would be enough,
but we don't have the battery technology.
And that's because Trump cut us off.
So I would say that what Lee Zeldin is doing
is very positive here because the CO2 climate
cultism was always a hoax.
That's not endangerment.
But you know what is endangerment is tariffs.
Tariffs are endangerment.
That's endangering the U.S. economy
by cutting us off from those intermediary technologies
that we need in order to achieve energy abundance
and also low cost energy.
I mean, think about it.
The competitiveness with China
is becoming a really critical issue.
For example, China recently announced
a new gas pipeline deal with Russia that will pipe.
I think it was 50 billion cubic meters of gas per year
from the Yamal gas fields, I believe, in Northwest Russia
across Mongolia into Northern China,
into the industrial center of the cities of Northern China.
That's dirt cheap energy.
Dirt cheap energy.
China's going to be paying a fraction of what Europe pays
or even a fraction of what America pays
because China's willing to engage in trade
and Trump won't allow trade with Russia or China.
So we end up, we, the American people,
we end up paying through the nose
while Trump's donors get rich
by selling overpriced gas to the world, including Europe
and ultimately what will become overpriced kilowatt hours
on the power grid, which is already happening
on the East Coast.
Those of you living on the East
or any of those 13 states
served by what is it, the JPM grid, I think it's called,
you're already paying double or triple
what you should be paying.
That's all, those are all stemming
from decisions made by either Trump or Biden.
Those decisions can be reversed, but they're not.
So you're going to keep paying through the nose.
The only good news to all of this is that
as battery technology becomes more widely available
and distributed, you'll be able to go
completely off grid pretty soon.
I'm anticipating within a couple of years,
you'll be able to buy a boatload of cheap solar,
funnel it into your own cheap sodium ion batteries
that will cycle for a hundred years
and also that don't explode and burn up in your garage.
And you'll be able to just cut yourself off from the grid
and just use sunlight to power everything
that you need for your home
because of the battery technology.
So the grid is becoming too expensive to use.
And between now and the year 2030.
I am predicting we're going to see a mass of people. Huge numbers of Americans are going to cut the cord to the power company
and they're going to go 100% off grid and I will be one of them and I'll tell you how it goes.
You know, I'll report everything that works because of course I'm up on this. I studied the battery chemistry.
You know, I keep up with news out of China. You know, I speak Chinese. I lived in Taiwan and you know, I'm monitoring the situation very closely
and as soon as we can get some viable grid shifting batteries that are economical and safe and can cycle effectively,
I'll bring you the news. In fact, I'll set up a whole demo for you. I'll set it up in my new studio.
We'll just demo the whole thing for you right there and maybe we'll just take the whole studio off the grid.
Just power the whole studio with nothing but solar and batteries to show you how it's done
and to show you how inexpensive it's going to become compared to what it has been in the past.
You know, previously, solar has never made economic sense. Not really. The payback time was too long, 20 or 25 years.
That's changing dramatically because of the rising cost of kilowatt hours of electricity.
So the payoff time of solar is shrinking to maybe seven years and it's going to shrink even more to five years or four years
and at some point it's just idiotic not to go completely off grid once the batteries are cheap and safe and effective
and the solar panels are cheap and effective, etc. And the real asset you're going to have is how much land you have
to where you can erect solar panels. So if you have a really tiny yard and a small roof, you know,
you can't really generate that much solar because there's a limit of how much efficiency
you can have for every square meter of sunshine that strikes your roof or strikes a solar panel
and that efficiency is not going to take huge leaps forward, by the way.
It's going to be around, I don't know, 30 to 34% or something in that range and that's about it.
You're not going to get 90% efficient solar panels ever. The physics don't work.
So you're going to get like 35% efficiency. So you're just going to need more land.
If you have more land, you can erect more solar panels. I mean, you just throw them out in the yard or whatever,
you know, put them on little cheap stands, whatever. They don't have to track or tilt or anything.
It'll all average out. You just, you know, based on your latitude, you know, you pick an angle
that works for most of the year or if you want to change the angle like twice a year,
you can increase efficiency 10 to 20%. But that's up to you. Nevertheless, the way this is going,
people are going to collect their own energy. They're going to store it in their own batteries
and then they're going to have their own local AI. They're going to power their AI from sunlight.
They're going to power their robots and their EVs from sunlight.
And even one of the things I'm looking forward to, I've mentioned before,
is because I own heavy equipment on my ranch, you know, like a skid steer and a mini excavator,
things like that for, you know, projects, moving dirt and doing permaculture, things like that.
And so I can't wait until those go battery powered because a battery powered excavator is actually
becoming viable. I used to mock such an idea a few years ago because, you know, it wasn't viable,
but it's going to become viable within a few years. And skid steers, same thing.
You'll be able to run on batteries for maybe one to two hours, which is fine for a lot of projects.
And then you plug it back in and you charge it, you know, that's fine.
Now tractors probably won't go solar or battery powered for a long time because they need very high energy density.
Tractors do a tremendous amount of work and burn a lot of diesel, but excavators do a lot less work.
I don't know if you know that, but, you know, a typical excavator might only have a 40 horsepower diesel engine in it.
And that's getting to the point where that can be replaced.
I'm talking about a mini excavator that can be replaced by batteries and you can charge your vehicles effectively with sunlight.
So that day is coming.
So maybe the greenies will will cheer people using solar and getting off grid because in that case you're not burning fossil fuels,
but you know the greenies that they they're just a cult anyway.
So you know their opinions don't matter.
They've never been rigorous thinkers.
I'm a rigorous thinker and I'm telling you that let's use combustion engines now while that's the technology in order to power our economy as we develop and deploy these other technologies,
but we have to have open global trade.
We have to stop the trade wars.
We have to stop the tariffs.
We have to stop the sanctions on Russia and the threats against China.
We got to trade with Russia and China.
If we want to have economic abundance in America and that's where Trump has gone wrong.
He's been picking an isolationist path, which is going to be catastrophic for our economy in my opinion.
So if he can open things up, then he actually could make America great again, at least economically speaking.
That's my take on it.
You can follow my work at naturalnews.com and you can hear more of my podcast and interviews at brighttion.com and I'm also launching a new video site.
Now it's called bright videos.com and it's sort of up and running right now.
It's not officially launched yet.
It's a little quirky, like the videos don't always play.
I'm vibe coding that thing.
So we'll let cloud code work on it and sort out the bugs, but that's coming.
So check it out and thank you for listening.
I'm Mike Adams and be well.
All right, hope you enjoyed that special report there.
A lot of good information.
And again, I do want to remind you that I'm publishing many articles per day now.
Sometimes, well, from two to five articles per day at naturalnews.com and the articles are extremely well sourced because I'm using my A.I. agents to do the sourcing now.
So it's really quite remarkable what I've been able to automate in terms of research and also, of course, I'm adding more science papers and more full length books to our in-house research index which you could take advantage of by either using our book creation engine,
which is at brightlearn.ai and all the books that you create also use our research database automatically and it's free.
And you can also use our A.I. deep research engine called bright answers.ai.
And that also uses the same database that I use for my research.
So, well, when I say database, I mean the same indexed.
It's a bunch of indexed documents is what it is like millions of millions of documents or tens of millions of pages of documents.
So just check that out.
Use those tools and also if you want to support us by the way shop with us at healthrangerstore.com because that's where we do our lab testing.
We have all our clean food and our supplements and personal care products ultra clean.
You know, I played 12 minutes of the lab tour for you the other day and I'm still going to release the full tour because I haven't shown you the sample prep room
and I haven't shown you the Fauci room where we do microbiology testing.
So that's coming up.
Can't wait to show you that.
And we've also got some really cool micro plastics research coming up probably within, I don't know, two weeks.
We're waiting on a part for the microscope to be able to nail it down correctly.
But shop with us healthrangerstore.com.
You'll get clean food and you'll help us financially support this platform and all the other platforms that we're building, which are focused on empowering humanity by passing censorship and bringing you truth and knowledge to empower you for a future where frankly probably a few billion humans won't make it.
You know, the ignorant ones who seem to be the majority.
You know, the future is not very good for people who don't know what's happening.
That that should be the understatement of the year.
But I mean, I consider that to be obvious and probably you do to kind of a self-evident statement, but a lot of people don't realize that.
So they're not going to be around probably in any case clean food is critical and I've got a special report for you here next.
I think I'll play it next about why glyphosate herbicide is often found in USDA organic foods.
So and then remember today we have the first half of the interview with former CIA counterterrorism case officer, John Kiriakou.
You don't want to miss that.
So stay tuned and enjoy the show.
A lot of people were shocked by the glyphosate findings in the common bread products.
These results were published by the state of Florida and they showed that certain brands of store-bought bread have seemingly crazy high levels of glyphosate, such as 191 parts per billion in some of them and maybe 170 parts per billion in others.
And then different brands had lower levels like 10 or 11 parts per billion.
I'm concerned about the 190 parts per billion.
That seems sort of alarmingly high and I'm a food scientist and thank you for listening.
I'm Mike Adams, the health ranger and you may know that I run a food science lab and I have for, I don't know.
What's it been almost 15 years now and I actually developed a method for testing for glyphosate.
Anyway, the thing you need to know in all of this is that USDA organic does not mean glyphosate free.
In fact, the organic sort of.
process for the USDA, which I'm quite familiar with, does not require any
glyphosate testing whatsoever. Now very few people are aware of this. It's a
shock to most people to find out that USDA certified organic requires no
testing for heavy metals, glyphosate, atrazine, frankly for anything. Because
the organic standard under USDA is not a standard of cleanliness or purity. It's
simply a certification of the process of farming. What it means is that the USDA
through its various certifiers is guaranteeing that the farmer has not
sprayed glyphosate on his or her crops. It doesn't mean the crops don't contain
glyphosate. Crops can contain glyphosate from lots of sources, including of course
just the wind carrying glyphosate from the field next door, but also in the water
supply. The irrigation can impart glyphosate into various foods and crops. So
unless you're testing for glyphosate, you don't really know how much is in it.
That makes sense, right? You don't really know. And a lot of these brands out there,
like the bread brands, with names, brand names that have the word nature or
natures or natural things like that in the product name. So you assume, oh, it's
you know, it's a natural sounding brand. It must be clean. That's the
assumption. But it turns out that's false because they can name their
company anything. Just having a name doesn't equal certification, doesn't
equal cleanliness or lab testing. And as far as I know, there are no bread
companies in America that test anything for glyphosate. Now, maybe they do
behind the scenes and I'm not aware of it, but I've never heard of any
company conducting glyphosate testing for their own bread products. Now, in
my lab, we test everything for glyphosate. It's one of our routine
tests. So if you actually want clean food that has been tested for heavy
metals and glyphosate and many other things, including E. coli and
salmonella shop with us health ranger store.com is where you find clean
food. Guaranteed clean food because in fact, I showed you the lab tour
video just the other day of our new laboratory facility. It's a
multi-million dollar lab building that's larger than most university
labs. It's extraordinary. Now, we don't make bread. But if we did make
bread, what we would do is when we acquire the wheat berries, we would
test the wheat berries before we use them to make the bread. And
that's what we do with our own products, you know, we test the
raw materials coming in before we use them in a formulation. Because
obviously, if the raw materials are contaminated, then the final
product is going to be contaminated. So what's happening is
these bread companies are just buying whatever the probably the
cheapest wheat is they can find wheat berries. They don't test
it. They don't know how much glyphosate is in it. So it goes
into the mix, you know, it's in the mixer bowl, and then
they're baking the bread and they make the bread and it's on the
shelf and it's nobody ever tested it. Even if it's certified
organic, the USDA never tested it, nor did the FDA. Now,
occasionally the FDA does spot check production of certain
types of foods. For example, they will show up from time to
time. They've done this at our facility. And they'll just
show up and say, oh, we're going to take a sample of this
and that and whatever we want. And you're going to
quarantine this for two weeks while we test it. And then
we're going to come back and tell you if you can release it
from quarantine. And as we've explained to the FDA in the
past, so well, we already tested it. And here's our test
results. So you don't need to go through this exercise
because we already know it's clean. And you know, here's
our lab, here's our test. And FDA is like, we don't care.
We're going to test it. We're just going to disrupt
your business because, you know, we're terrorists. You
know, that's, that's what the FDA does. And we're
terrorists, we run around the country terrorizing small
businesses. So we end up having to put that stuff into
quarantine for a couple of weeks. And then the FDA comes
back and says, yep, it's clean. We're like, yeah, we know, we
already know, because we tested it before you tested it. But
they don't care. However, you could argue that what
they're doing does make sense. For some companies, if there
are food manufacturers out there that are bad faith
operators, let's say, like a peanut butter maker, that
gets a discount on a bunch of peanuts, because it's
laced with aflatoxins or E coli, for that matter. Like here,
Oh, discount peanuts. Yeah, somebody got crapped all over
the peanuts. So it's like peanut feces brew. And it's at a
discount today. And some peanut butter company, you
know, some small brand maybe will buy that up is like, Oh,
we saved a bunch of money. Yeah, it's like, yeah, it's
it's not even peanut, but it's poo butter. And it kills
old ladies, you know, who eat it and it has the E coli in it.
And then then the especially the elderly get sick and die. So the
FDA shown up and testing their product, you could argue that
well, okay, maybe that's that establishes some level of, of
safety. Okay, but I would argue that the court system
already makes companies pay dearly if they are bad faith
operators using contaminated raw materials. Nevertheless, this
is how the system works. But then again, the same FDA that
claims it's keeping peanut butter safe, will approve toxic
vaccines that killed 1.5 million Americans. So kind of takes all
the air out of their argument that Oh, we're saving lives and
protecting people's health. No, you're not your overall, you're
just killing people. And you're approving toxic deadly
bio weapons that also kill people. So so no, if there
were no FDA, we'd all be better off in the aggregate. Yeah,
there might be some poo butter that slips through from some
unscrupulous operator out there. But they wouldn't stay in
business for very long because you know, the internet and the
word would spread. So really, we don't need the FDA anymore
like we used to. Nevertheless, I'm getting off topic. The
point is the USDA doesn't test. The FDA largely doesn't
test. Occasionally they do. And most of the manufacturers of
food products also do not test. So and this can affect organic
also. So if you're buying food from a grocery store, I mean,
it's it's like a minefield. It's a minefield of toxins. You
you never know what you're going to get. It's like forest
gump and a box of chocolates. You never know what you're
going to get. Jenny, I was running and running and running.
Sorry, that's my forest gump impression. Me and Jenny, we was
like peas and carrots. Alright, enough forest gump. Tom Hanks
there. Anyway, you get the idea. The food supply is a
treacherous vortex of unsafe substances and toxins. And if
you want clean food, you got to get it from companies that
actually do the testing. So I mean, that's us for sure. We you
know that I've shown you the videos. We have all the
documents. We do all the testing every single day. I was
just in the lab, like 30 minutes ago, by the way, we have a
technician there, doing preventative maintenance of one
of our ICP instruments kind of cool. She was showing me one
of the octopoles. It's like, oh, we don't normally see
those outside of the instrument. So that's interesting. But
anyway, we sell clean food at health rangers store.com. We do
our own testing because we don't trust anybody else. And that is
a stance that is well justified because you really can't
trust anybody. If you can't trust suppliers, you know, so we
got to test it ourselves. And that's what we do. So you
can support us at health rangers store.com. And thank
you for listening. You can also follow my work at
naturalnews.com. I'm Mike Adams, the health ranger. Take
care. So it looks almost certain now that Trump is going to
order the US military to bomb Iran or strike it with missiles.
And that that's going to set off a chain reaction of events
which will lead to Trump's political downfall. But even
so he's doing it because Netanyahu holds something over
Trump that's so damning or so powerful or so compelling that
Trump must obey Netanyahu. In fact, Netanyahu has taken a trip
to the United States. Again, he's arriving in order to
clearly deliver a final threat to Donald Trump, which is if
you don't order the bombing of Iran, then this is what's
going to happen. And you can imagine it's probably not too
difficult to figure out what that is. It's going to involve
a lot of blackmail material on Trump and the people around
him, maybe things related to the Epstein files, maybe records of
financial transactions or whatever dirt that Israel has on
Trump or the Trump family, they're going to leverage all of
it to try to push Trump into this war with Iran, which
benefits Israel but does not benefit the United States. Now
I recently interviewed John Kiriakou, former
CIA, a counterterrorism case officer, and he agrees with me that Netanyahu has something
on Trump, a lot of arm twisting going on, and he also agreed with me that if the U.S. takes
a lot of casualties or loses a stealth bomber or if a U.S. naval vessel is destroyed or
something on that magnitude, then the political fallout for Trump would be absolutely catastrophic
and probably also for the GOP, but especially for Trump himself, who might not survive the
rest of the year in office. He might be impeached or just forced to resign. And that seems to be
an increasingly likely outcome of this. It's not a certainty, but it's likely because
China has given Iran these advanced anti-stealth radar systems and air defense systems that can
take out stealth bombers and stealth fighters, et cetera. So if the U.S. tries to attack Iran,
they could lose aircraft. If they lose stealth aircraft, then the political fallout in the
United States would be absolutely tremendous. And the calculation in Trump's mind on this
has to be really frightening. The way I see it in Trump's mind, if he doesn't attack Iran,
then Israel releases whatever blackmail they have on him or his family members or they attack
the stock market or they crash the banking system or whatever they're capable of doing,
they control a lot of things. But if Trump does attack Iran and if it goes badly,
where thousands of U.S. soldiers end up getting killed in the Iranian retaliation,
let's say, then Trump's political career is over, most likely. So in his mind, he's thinking
that whatever Netanyahu has on Trump is so bad that he's willing to risk his political life
in order to avoid Netanyahu releasing whatever that stuff is. Look, Netanyahu is a thug.
And I think Trump knows that. It's just that Trump is caught up in the thug's web here because
so many of the donors that put Trump into office were pro-Israel Zionist donors.
Almost all of Trump's cabinet and office personnel are loyal to Netanyahu, more than they are loyal to
Trump. It's clear, for example, that Pam Bondi doesn't take orders from Trump. She takes orders
from Netanyahu, period. And even some suspected people like Susie Wiles, who is part of Trump's
staff in the White House, she used to run Netanyahu's presidential campaign.
And there are many other examples of this. And then there's also the crazies, like Marc Levin,
and the Ben Shapiro's, like the crazy lunatics who want to start World War because it's part of
their weird end of days religious cultism or fanaticism or whatever you want to call it.
There's those people, too. So Trump is in a difficult position. Damned if you do,
damned if you don't. The thing is, if he does attack Iran, not only is he damned,
but America is damned because the blowback against the United States will be tremendous.
For example, energy prices will skyrocket because of the Strait of Hormuz.
There will be casualties of American soldiers at U.S. bases across the Middle Eastern region,
including in Iraq and Qatar and the UAE or Saudi Arabia or just all over the entire region,
wherever those bases are, they're scattered across the whole region. And every single one
of those bases is within range of Iran's missiles, every single one of them.
In addition, U.S. naval vessels are within reach of many of Iran's missiles,
including hypersonic missiles. And it's doubtful that U.S. naval vessels can effectively defend
themselves against a barrage of such missiles being launched by Iran. In addition, Iran has
new missile technology that they did not have six or seven months ago, or I guess it's almost
eight months now since June of last year. And that means that the United States military
probably does not have a good idea of the full capabilities of Iran, especially with its anti-ship
missiles. And yes, I'm using the word missile deliberately here because Iran has anti-ship
missiles as well as, of course, anti-ship drones and drone swarms. And as we saw in the exchange
with Israel last summer, that Iran will fill the skies with hundreds of drones,
and then they'll have some very intelligent missiles kind of mixed in with the drones
to where the defense systems of the U.S. Navy, let's say, are occupied trying to take out all
the drones, which are cheap and expendable. And then that allows, and then that distraction
allows the guided missiles, or rockets, or the more capable drones to be able to penetrate
the airspace and effectively make it to their target and detonate as kamikaze drones. So
the U.S. government, I believe, especially the Department of Defense,
is very likely overestimating its capabilities both offensively and defensively.
And even though Israel wants regime change in Iran, or to split up the country,
it seems like bombing Iran is only going to achieve the opposite,
which is hardening domestic support for the current Iranian leadership.
In fact, the most likely regime change that's going to happen from this is in America,
where Trump will end up having to be having to resign. He'll be forced out of power
because of the mess that he made in Iran. Now that's not going to happen overnight,
and it's not a certainty, but it's one of the increasingly likely outcomes that this
could be the end of Trump. Netanyahu doesn't care because he controls the next guy just the
same. So to Netanyahu, Trump is expendable. And to Netanyahu, America is expendable.
What matters to him is just how much damage we can do to Iran as long as Israel can survive.
And, you know, chaos is the name of the game for Israel. They just want mass chaos in Iran
because chaos breeds instability, and instability allows Israel and Mossad
to assert much more effective control over the region, which is what they want.
So, but the backlash against Israel could be catastrophic for Israel if Iran is able to launch
its own retaliatory missiles. So unless the U.S. has such a massive first strike that obliterates
Iran's entire field of missiles and, you know, all the mountain bases and everything else,
then Iran is going to get off a retaliatory attack, and they promise that they will target
Israel with that attack. So therefore, Israel could actually face extreme devastation
in retaliation, even if Israel does not itself take part in the initial attack on Iran,
because Iran has stated through their various foreign ministers or whatever the correct titles
are that they consider Israel to be a proxy state of the United States. If the U.S. attacks Iran,
in their mind, Israel is a legitimate military target, and so is every U.S. military base
across the entire region. So Trump is walking into a trap, and it's a trap that could devastate
the world economy. It could devastate energy supplies for numerous nations and regions around
the world, including Western Europe. And it could lead to mass inflation. It could lead to
disruptions in economies. And on top of that, it could lead to the loss of thousands of U.S.
soldiers, their lives. And if it goes horribly wrong to the point where the world sees the U.S.
military as now being weak because Iran managed to do something like sink a naval vessel or
completely nullify an aircraft carrier or something like that, then that's going to change the way
the world sees the strength of the United States. And that will have repercussions in terms of the
world abandoning the dollar as the reserve currency or really, we shouldn't call it
reserve currency, the common trading currency. So all of this is intertwined. And again, Trump is
walking into a trap. And the only way for America to win here is to not play the game. The only way
for America to win is to tell Netanyahu to go pound sand and do not attack Iran, bring the
soldiers back home and focus on trade instead of war. But Netanyahu doesn't want that. He wants war
and chaos. He wants blood spilled on the lands of Iran.
and who knows anywhere else across the Middle East,
as they've already done in destroying Gaza.
And let's be very clear and upfront about this.
Israel is a satanic regime, you know,
run by actual Satanists.
And of course they want death and suffering and chaos.
And so Trump, if he is to pass the most important test
of his life in the eyes of God,
Trump must resist the Satanists
and reject Israel's demands for war
and suffering and death and destruction.
If Trump can't do that,
it doesn't matter whether he wins the Nobel Peace Prize
because he will lose the ultimate prize in the eyes of God.
Trump will have forfeited his soul's eternal reward
if it's not already forfeit, I suppose.
Or at least that's the view that makes sense to me.
But what do you think?
Let me know.
And you can catch all of my articles at naturalnews.com.
You can catch more of my videos at brighttion.com
or the new site coming up brightvideos.com
which has AI-powered features.
And you can use all of my AI engine tools
at brightanswers.ai or brighttion.ai.
So thank you for listening and I pray for peace.
Take care.
I learned that the Ring Doorbell Company
ran an ad during the recent Super Bowl
which of course I did not watch
because you know, what's the point?
But Ring ran an ad that said
that if you install this surveillance doorbell
that it's gonna help you find lost pets.
And so they depicted lost dogs and cats
that were found because some other neighbors
Ring Doorbell video managed to capture
and then they were able to identify the dog
and return it to its owner.
Oh, such a heartwarming story.
But of course, you'd have to be an idiot
to think that that's what this is all about.
Yes, it's a surveillance grid
but it's not about finding pets.
It's about tracking you.
It's a human surveillance grid.
And what's amazing about Ring
is that people are willing to pay
for their own imprisonment and surveillance.
The people are willing to buy a product
that violates their own privacy
and they install it themselves.
I mean, gosh, the CIA must be laughing
their heads off right now.
I'm thinking, oh my God,
we managed to convince the American people
to spy on each other
and they pay for the hardware.
Oh my God, it's so hilarious.
That's exactly what Ring is.
And of course, I've warned people for many, many years,
don't put an Amazon Alexa device in your house.
Why?
Because it's obviously listening to you 24 seven
and uploading all the audio to Amazon servers.
And the CIA is Amazon's largest client
for its AWS hosting system.
So you're basically just uploading all your talk
directly to the CIA, huh?
And then, you know, the typical American respondents
is like, well, I have nothing to hide.
I don't care if they listen to everything I'm saying.
I don't have anything to hide.
No, that's actually that's not the right answer.
The answer is you're not important enough
to be blackmailed yet.
So everybody has something private
that they don't want to make public.
Whether it's just something they say
in the privacy of their own home
or a joke they told at home
that they would never tell publicly
or even just acts like sitting naked on the toilet, you know?
You don't want that all over the internet, probably.
Just guessing, unless you work for Onlyfans or something.
Maybe you could get paid for that, but I doubt it.
So you have these just brain dead Americans
who are willing to give up their privacy
and even pay for the surveillance grid.
And they don't think there's anything wrong with that.
But there are some now more and more waking up
and saying, wait a second, you know,
they saw the Super Bowl ad and, you know,
at their 85 IQ started a couple of brain nodes
started to fire off like, oh my God,
they could spy on us too.
Like, yes, what took you so long?
So the ring commercial is having the opposite effect.
It's actually causing more people to pledge
that they will never buy ring cameras
or ring doorbells or whatever they are
because they don't wanna install a surveillance grid.
Yeah, good for them.
Again, what took you so long?
So if you have a smart TV, it's watching you,
classic Orwellian, and it's got an internet connection.
Why?
Because it's watching you.
It's got a camera on the front.
Why?
Because it's watching you.
Duh!
You know, Amazon Alexa, it's listening to you.
The Nest devices that are the temperature control,
you know, thermostat, they have microphones in them,
by the way, that's already been proven.
So they're listening also
and they're connected to the internet.
So they're uploading all your audio.
All this is collected and used as blackmail
against everybody.
Just in case you ever become a member of Congress
or just in case you ever become a Supreme Court justice
or a senator or a governor
or a corporate leader or whatever,
they can open up all your files
and go all the way back through everything you ever said.
They can have AI analysis.
Like, is there anything that's blackmailable?
And find a bunch of stuff that you said
and then approach you and say,
oh, look, hey, we have all these recordings of stuff
you said for the last 20 years
because you were dumb enough
to install surveillance items in your own home.
Yeah, we have all those files.
And now you're gonna do what we say
or we're gonna start leaking these
to TMZ or whoever.
And your whole reputation is gonna be destroyed.
You're gonna lose your wife,
you're gonna lose your job,
you're gonna lose your reputation, et cetera.
That's how it actually works.
So when you run around installing
a surveillance grid product in your home,
you are feeding the beast
that is the blackmail beast.
You could call it like Epstein light.
They're not catching you, you know,
raping little kids.
Hopefully you don't do that in your home.
But they are catching you saying things
and doing things and looking in certain ways
that if leaked could destroy you.
So it's all a blackmail grid.
And by the way,
almost all the major VPN companies are owned by Zionists.
They're owned by, you know, essentially Mossad.
And they're just honeypot traps.
They're not really VPNs.
I mean, yeah, they do hide your IP,
but they are there to hoover up
everything that you're doing online.
They've got your name,
they've got a tied to your credit card.
They know all the porn sites that you visited.
They know all the quirky little porn search terms
that you typed in if you do that kind of thing.
Like, I don't know what are some of the,
like Midget Granny porn or whatever, you know?
That's almost too funny.
But whatever, they've got it all.
They know exactly what you're doing.
And it's all, it goes back to Mossad.
And so again, that's Epstein light.
You gotta understand the way that Zionists operate,
the way Mossad works is always about blackmail.
If they can trap you,
if you're a high level person
and they can trap you into some kind of,
you know, rape videos or something,
well, they'll use that on you.
If you're a lower level person
and they find something embarrassing in your browser
or in your search history,
or, you know, because you thought
you were secretly using a VPN
when you were searching for Midget Granny porn.
And then it turns out that,
oh, that's all owned by Mossad.
So they got all that.
They're gonna use that against you.
They're gonna compromise you.
If they can't compromise you,
they're gonna compromise one of your family members
because your family member,
their browsing history has also been hoovered up
by the same group.
So they'll say, oh, look, you know,
your wife, your son, your niece,
your sister, your whatever, your daughter.
Look, we got all their stuff.
And oh, look what they're doing.
Oh, illegal drug use.
Oh, wouldn't want that to come out.
So you're gonna do what we say.
That's how it works.
So if you're using Ring Doorbells
or Amazon, Alexa or smart TVs
or, you know, that are connected to the internet,
I mean, it's okay to buy a smart TV
as long as it doesn't have an internet connection.
Don't give it your wifi for God's sake.
That's just retarded.
But people do this all the time.
They install surveillance grids in their own home
and then they wonder why their privacy is violated.
It's insane.
So just say no to the surveillance grid.
Say no to all that technology.
And be smart about this.
Be smart, be informed.
If you wanna stay informed, you know,
listen to my podcast here, naturalnews.com.
And I'm also launching a new video site
called brightvideos.com, which should be functional.
So check it out.
How could it possibly be in the United States
national interest to initiate another war of choice?
It can't be.
It's not an art.
It's not.
It's actually contradicts our interests
of trying to keep energy prices low.
100% correct.
The Iranian.
are no threat to us. And if the Israelis really believe that the Iranians are an existential
threat to them, then maybe they should engage with the Omanis, or the Algerians, or the Saudis,
or the Emiratis, or even the Qataris to try to come to some sort of a diplomatic solution.
But Netanyahu flying to the United States every two months and begging whoever happens to be
president to destroy Iran for him. That's just not, that's not in the U.S.'s national interest.
Welcome to today's interview here on Breitian.com. I'm Mike Adams, the founder of Breitian.
And today we're joined by a very special person, a first-time guest here
on the show, but someone who I must have seen a hundred of his interviews. And his name is John
Kiriakou. And he's a former CIA counterterrorism case officer, earlier an analyst, and he's got some
wildly popular, successful podcasts on Spotify and Apple. We'll get to some of that. He joins us today
to talk about what's happening in the Middle East and around the world. Welcome, Mr. Kiriakou.
It's a pleasure to have you on today. Thank you. Thank you. The pleasure is all mine.
It's good to see you. Well, look, it's just, I'm honored that you're here because as I've
even said on my own podcast, I said, I like this guy. I like your message. I like your humanity.
I like the fact that you are a critical thinker, that you're not, you don't have party loyalty
or person loyalty, but rather principles loyalty. And that's, that's all that counts right now.
You want to give us a little background for our audience? Sure. I joined the CIA just out
of graduate school in January of 1990. I spent the first seven and a half years of my career
as an analyst working exclusively on Iraq. And then I made kind of an unusual change to
counterterrorist operations. I ended up being the chief of CIA counterterrorism operations
in Pakistan after the 9-11 attacks. Wow. And yeah, it was, it was quite, quite the job.
I would imagine. And then went into the private sector for a few years then to the
Senate Foreign Relations Committee as the senior investigator there working on counterterrorism,
counter narcotics, things like that, piracy, international piracy. I blew the whistle on
the CIA's torture program in 2007. And the Obama administration in 2012 arrested me,
charged me with five felonies, including three counts of espionage. I ended up taking a plea
to a lesser charge just to make the thing go away. I had five kids at home. But I said that the CIA
was torturing its prisoners. I said that torture was official U.S. government policy.
And the policy had been approved by the president himself. I would do it again today
if I had the opportunity. I have zero regrets. And got out of prison 11 years ago. And since then,
I've written, wow, nine books. And I've got my podcasts. And yeah, you know,
a little bit here and a little bit there. Yeah, together living.
Well, you're doing an extraordinary job. And I think people are really resonating
with your message. And it seems like it's time. You know, we've all lived through the,
you know, the Bush era and the Obama era that you that you saw. And then the first
Trump era, etc. I mean, we've lived through this and not that much has changed, except it's all
seemingly gotten worse. So how would you characterize today's Trump administration?
You know, just just in the context of being humanitarian or following the rule of law or
respecting the Constitution. Where are we in history with this Trump administration
compared to where we were when you were blowing the whistle?
That's actually a pretty tough question.
MAGA as a MAGA as an ideology is something that I think many, many Americans can agree with.
I've long maintained, and you may have seen me say this in other podcasts, but I've long
maintained that the ideological spectrum is not a straight line from left to right.
It's a circle. And at some point it meets the left and the right meet. In the case of MAGA and
the progressive left, I think that that is on issues of war and peace. There were celebrations
when the president announced a mere six or seven months ago that he wanted to cut the Pentagon
budget by 50%. But then just a couple of months later, he said he wanted to increase the
Pentagon budget by 50%. You can't be both a neocon and a MAGA Republican at the same time.
My friends on the left would disagree with me if I said that that I believed that
the Trump administration would go down in history as one of the more humanitarian
administrations. I don't think that it will, but that's not to say that it's necessarily
a bad thing. Because on the other side, on the flip side, open borders aren't humanitarian for
anybody. And so we have to make a decision. The point that I think you were alluding to
is the fact that we are an incredibly divided nation. I'm 61 years old. I vaguely remember
1968 and 1969. I remember sitting on my dad's lap and asking him why so many buildings were
burning on TV. And he told me that some bad men had killed Martin Luther King and Robert Kennedy
and people were very upset. I don't think we've been so divided since 1968 or 1969. I mean,
think the Kent State uprising and shootings, for example. We don't have to be there.
I think that the political parties have put us there. And I believe that we shouldn't be
loyal to political parties. We should be loyal to the Constitution. We should be loyal to the country,
loyal to the idea that this really is the greatest nation on earth. And I think people get distracted
by this political silliness. Okay. Thank you for that detailed and thoughtful answer.
Now, let's let's apply that to the situation in the Middle East where, from my perspective,
and feel free to correct me, you know, this is this, this is a conversation and you can,
you can tell me I'm wrong. I mean, you actually, you know more about this than I do by far. So
my perception is that Trump is about to attack Iran because Netanyahu is twisting his arm and
making him do it. That's the story right there. That's it. Is that it? That is it. That is the truth.
I'm going to ask you a rhetorical question. How could it possibly be in the in the United States
national interest to initiate another war of choice? It can't be. It's not an interest. No,
it's not. It's not. It's actually contradicts our interests of trying to keep energy prices
low. Hundred percent correct. 100 percent correct. I feel very strongly about this.
The Iranians are no threat to us. And if the Israelis really believe that the Iranians are an
existential threat to them, then maybe they should engage with the Omanis or the Algerians
or the Saudis or the Emirates or even the Qataris to try to come to some sort of a diplomatic
solution. But Netanyahu flying to the United States every two months and begging whoever happens to be
president to destroy Iran for him, that's just not that's not in the U.S. national interest.
No, I have five children. I have four sons. All of them are of military age. Well,
that's not true. Three of the four are of military age. I wouldn't want my sons
fighting and dying in Iran to protect Israel's, you know, what the Israeli government believes
is its long term security goal. But the Israelis go fight that fight.
Another thing, too, is I believe when Donald Trump talks about the the Nobel Peace Prize,
you know, you get so much guff in the press. But I think Donald Trump probably deserves
the Nobel Peace Prize. And if he were able to negotiate some sort of an agreement with the
Iranians, it should be hands down a done deal. And I'll add, people forget that he was the one
who mandated negotiations between the Democratic Republic of Congo and Rwanda. Number one,
same thing between Cambodia and Thailand. Number two, I mean, we can go all around the world.
There have been seven or eight of them all around the world. They're not headline makers,
but he's the one that ordered these negotiations, these diplomatic talks that have
resulted in peace. Well, we used to say in the 1970s, and I learned this in
college in the 1980s, only Nixon could go to China, right? Only the most virulently anti-Chinese
president could make peace with China. Maybe only Trump can go to Tehran.
Okay. But his, let me let me ask you a follow up on that. He keeps saying he wants Iran to do a
deal, but really he wants Iran to surrender to his terms. And his terms are absolutely unacceptable.
They're not even his. They're Benjamin Netanyahu's terms.
But including the missiles, you can't give up the missiles if you're a sovereign nation
because then you would be destroyed.
So how does Trump expect anyone to agree to these terms?
This is literally the one thing about Donald Trump that I just simply don't understand.
I don't understand why he is so susceptible to pressure from Benjamin Netanyahu.
You're exactly right.
The Israeli government demands are clear.
They've made them public and that is no uranium enrichment period, no ballistic missiles period.
And you're right.
You cease to be a country if you can't defend yourself and can't have a missile system.
So what is that?
The Israelis have also talked increasingly less discreetly about the end goal being
to divide Iran up into five small countries.
There would be Balochistan, Arabistan, Kurdistan, you know, five little rump countries because
then they're much more easily controlled.
The Israelis have good relations with Azerbaijan, for example.
They have a base in Azerbaijan from which they can attack Iran.
They have good relations with Iran and Iraq's Kurds.
They're funding the Mujahideen-e-Khalq, the MEK terrorist group that we're now
in bed with.
So I think that this end goal of the Israelis to carve up Iran into five different countries
is what they're going to try to eventually get Donald Trump to do.
And this is nothing but catastrophe for all of us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That makes sense to me what you just said there.
So let me add this question into it.
Is it possible that Trump and the DOD are fantastically underestimating the increased weapons potential
of Iran even since last June because of technology shipments from both China and Texas from Russia?
Exactly.
Plus, Iran's own domestic engineering capabilities, which are significant and very smart engineers
and mathematicians, right?
So it seems to me like I'm hearing from Trump and I'm hearing from the MAGA people
like, yeah, America, we're the best.
We're undefeatable.
And I'm starting to think like, well, what about the laws of physics?
You know, hypersonic missiles, ballistic missiles, anti-ship missiles, et cetera.
Where do you even start?
Right.
Hypersonic missiles.
We don't have hypersonics yet.
We're experimenting with them, but we don't have hypersonics yet.
The Iranians do.
They've tested them.
Number one.
Right.
You remember prior to the 12-day war, the Israelis bombed Iran, and the Iranians responded with
something like 600 drones.
These were slow-motion drones called suicide drones, so they're not going to come back.
They just crash into whatever the target is.
They warned the Israelis in advance that the drones were coming, and they did that
just because they had to save face domestically.
Like, well, the Israelis attacked us, so now we're going to attack them with
these drones.
They warned the Israelis through the Jordanians that the drones were coming.
All the drones were shot down, but seven out of, I think it was 600.
That's actually valuable intelligence, that the Israeli Iron Dome is not perfect and
seven slow-motion drones that you have watched for the past six hours try to make their
way across Iraq and across Jordan, and you still couldn't shoot it down.
And shooting down the other drones costs a billion dollars or something.
And that was my second point.
Right.
The reason why that war only lasted 12 days was because the Israelis ran out of missiles.
They're just out.
They used them all.
And have they had a chance to replenish them?
We don't know, but a lot of observers say no.
In the meantime, you've made an important point that sanctions, which have gone on for 47 years
now, have forced the Iranians to fend for themselves, right?
So if they have a need for something that they can't buy because of sanctions, they
just make it themselves, and they've become quite good at it.
All that with the technology that they are able to procure from China and Russia, and
the Iranians want for nothing.
They're prepared for the Israelis.
Also, Iran is a country of 92 million people, and it's the size of Germany.
This is a major country we're talking about.
It's not just going to collapse because you fire a rocket at it.
That's right.
You're going to have to commit ground troops.
And I don't think that as a country, we have the stomach for something like that.
Well, let me go back to something you just said.
You're really talking about the economic asymmetry of how Iran can launch low cost
drones that require Israel to defend with extremely high cost interceptors.
But I want to add another element to this and ask you about your knowledge on this.
The interceptors, which are mostly manufactured by U.S. weapons companies, they rely,
of course, very heavily on these so-called rare earths that China has slapped major export
restrictions on, including everything from gallium and dysprosium and neodymium and magnets
and guidance and radar systems.
And all of these elements are extremely highly restricted.
Now, there's been a pass on some of those elements until the end of this year, but
China could revoke that pass at any time in addition to selling off U.S. treasuries
and whatever else.
So China has a lot of cards to play.
If the U.S. attacks Iran, wouldn't China say, well, we can't let Iran fall because it's
the gateway between the East and the Middle and Africa and Europe and everything?
So we're just going to use economic weapons and resource weapons of restrictions
against the United States.
And then the U.S. won't be able to build the interceptors to give to Israel
to defend itself against Iran.
Does that make sense?
You see, that makes perfect sense.
It's not just a question of, oh, should we hit them or should we not hit them?
There are an awful lot of moving parts in this.
And one of the things that the Chinese saw early on was the value,
the import of rare earth metals.
We were getting most of our rare earth metals from the Congo when that was a country.
They're just flush with rare earth metals.
But the problem with rare earths, they exist all over the place.
We even have them under the Salton Sea in the California desert.
They're very, very expensive to mine because most of what you mine with rare
earths is just waste.
It's rock and sand and it's just wasted.
So it costs you more to mine it than the value of the finished ore.
Well, the Chinese are willing to take that economic loss because first,
their economy is very robust and they have the money.
They spend literally a fraction, less than a 10 percent of what
we spend on national defense or about 10 percent of what we spend on national
defense and it allows them to control the entire world market for rare earth metals.
So what happens then, as you just posed, when we attack Iran on behalf of Israel,
we fight Israel's battle for it.
And then the Chinese cut us off from the sale of rare earth metals.
What are we going to use for missile guidance systems?
Or cell phones or the computers that run our cars?
You made a second point that I think bears repeating.
The Chinese are, depending on what numbers you're looking at,
the second or third largest holder of long term government treasury bonds.
If the Chinese really want to put the pain to us,
they can just dump those bonds and our entire economy would crash.
So, you know, is it really worth it?
Do we really want to do this?
Besides the fact that you're probably not going to get your Nobel Peace Prize
for waging a war of choice.
But see these these repercussions that you mentioned, these are costs
to America, but not costs to Netanyahu.
So from Netanyahu's point of view, he doesn't care if he throws
America under the bus or if America bleeds out economically, right?
As long as Israel gets what he wants, which is chaos in the Middle East.
See, but you can't say that out loud because then you're an anti-Semite.
You know, I said exactly the same thing a few weeks ago.
And the Israeli Foreign Minister's political director wrote an article
saying that I was a noted anti-Semite.
And I was like, what?
Well, the but the word is lost all meaning now.
Yes, it has just like sanctions, you know,
sanctions sort of sort of forced the the Iranians to stand on their
own or their own two feet, calling everybody who disagrees with one
of your policies in anti-Semite has made the meaning worthless.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
And also sanctions didn't work against Russia.
It just made Russia's domestic industry stronger.
Well, Foreign Minister Lavrov said two things.
He said, number one, the Russians were surprised at the swiftness
with which the Americans implemented sanctions.
He said that just a week after the sanctions were announced.
And then a year or two later, he said he was surprised at the quickness
with which the Russians were able to get around sanctions.
Let me add one other thing.
I went to China last year on a business trip.
It's the first time I had ever been to China.
And I had trouble finding places that would take a visa or a master card.
But everybody took this thing called the octopus card.
So finally, I asked one of the shopkeepers,
what is this octopus card I keep seeing everywhere?
He said, oh, that's that's kind of our national credit card of China.
I said.
Why don't you just use MasterCard and Visa?
And he said, because MasterCard and Visa
put every transaction through New York,
which makes it susceptible to American sanctions.
He said, octopus card goes through Shanghai.
So we don't have to worry about American sanctions.
And that is what happens when you overuse
and overimpose sanctions.
Yes, yes.
Okay, now speaking of China,
we've all seen China shipping many cargo planes
of equipment to Iran.
And according to reports,
I've done a lot of research on this.
It appears that those include both anti-stealth radar systems
as well as ground-based interceptors
that can independently track
and take down stealth bombers and stealth fighters.
Now, what's interesting to me
is that the anti-stealth radar claims
to have a 500 kilometer detection range.
It's amazing.
Isn't it though?
I mean, and that eliminates the ability
of what Trump did last June,
bombing Fordo and others.
But there's one more thing that wraps all this together, John,
which is that if we were to lose a stealth bomber,
I don't think we could replace it now
because it uses so many rare earths
and it also uses graphite.
And China has a near 100% global control
over the graphite industry.
And the US is 100% import dependent on graphite
and many of the rare metals.
So unless we have stockpiles sitting around somewhere,
if we start losing stealth fighters or stealth bombers
or even F-35s, I'm not sure how those can be replaced.
What do you think?
I have to agree with you.
If we were to lose a stealth fighter,
it would be just devastating.
And if this is true,
what we're hearing about the Chinese
and Chinese military shipments to Iran,
the Iranians are gonna be far better prepared
than we've given them credit for being.
The Iranian policy as we've seen it
over the last several years
has been something called strategic patience.
That's what they've called it, strategic patience.
They've been willing to take blows from the Israelis.
They've been willing to just sit by
as literally their entire top military leadership
was taken out in a series of Israeli attacks.
All of their, not all,
almost all of their top nuclear scientists
have been assassinated one at a time,
close in assassinations in Tehran,
as well as overseas when they're attending conferences
or meetings, for example, and they don't retaliate.
Well, the Iranian government is far more patient
than the Iranian people.
And the Iranian people have been demanding retaliation.
We keep getting attacked.
What are you gonna do about it?
And so the government is in the position now
where it's going to have to fight that fight
if the Israelis and or the Americans launch something new.
And if they do launch something new
and the Iranians really do put up a fight
that might include the use of Chinese technology,
which believe me, the Chinese would love to see tested
on the battlefield since they're not testing it
on the battlefield now.
Because there is no Chinese battlefield.
Right, because they're not invading their neighbors.
Then what do we do?
We're screwed.
Exactly, they're not invading their neighbors.
They're not invading their neighbors, right?
Like I say all the time that the American defense budget
is bigger than the next eight largest countries combined.
Right?
Right.
And then we wonder why we have such hideous
user unfriendly airports.
Why are roads and highways are afflicted
with potholes everywhere?
Why are bridges are falling down
into the rivers beneath them?
Why are hospitals are understaffed, overcrowded
and 20 years behind the times
because we spend everything on the Pentagon budget?
Because we've convinced ourselves
that we have to be the policemen of the world,
whether the world wants it or likes it or not.
And why don't we have bullet trains, for example?
But those expenditures are not even efficient, right?
No, they're not.
Because most of that's waste and fraud and grift.
Yes it is.
I mean, look at how Russia,
with a fraction of the US military budget
can come up with not only the Kinzal hypersonic missiles
but the Oreshnik system.
You're exactly right.
Which is revolutionary and using non-nuclear
high energy kinetic impacts
that do not violate any kind of nuclear treaties.
Not that any of those are even enforced anymore
since recently.
But you see what I'm saying.
I mean, with 1.5 trillion dollars
we should have like Star Trek technology,
photon torpedoes or something.
Exactly right.
Instead we have garbage.
You know, people say all the time,
well, you don't know what DARPA's working on.
And I always say, but that's the point.
Whatever DARPA's working on,
they should have developed it 20 years ago,
it should be out today.
And it should be Star Trek kind of stuff.
And it's not.
It's not.
You know, we've been told for decades
they're working on this robot.
It's gonna make soldiers obsolete.
They just need to figure out the battery.
Well, you know what?
The South Koreans figured out the battery.
And now South Korea,
I should say Hyundai's a subsidiary in South Korea
that builds robots.
It was highlighted in the Wall Street Journal
over the weekend.
They're ready to go to market with their robots
with long life batteries
that can do things like get in a self-driving car
and go do your grocery shopping.
Yeah, yeah.
How come we don't have that?
Have you seen?
Why hasn't DARPA figured that out?
China, two of China's top companies,
BYD and CATL, CATL, right?
I mean, their battery technology
is 20 years ahead of anything in AWS.
State of the art.
When I went to China last year,
I said to a member of our group
who was from Hong Kong,
she's an attorney.
I said, what is this car, this BYD?
She said, yeah, it stands for Beyond Your Dreams.
It's our electric car.
I said, this car is gorgeous.
They're amazing.
The design, it's just beautiful to look at.
And she said, yeah, they're really cheap.
They're gonna be the number one car
in a lot of different countries around the world.
And they're now number one in Canada,
number one in Australia,
number one in New Zealand.
Sales are booming in Europe.
I said, I've never heard of this car.
We don't have these in the United States.
And she said, because you guys banned them
from the United States to protect Tesla.
Well, these cars are a third, a fourth
of the cost of a Tesla.
And they're better than Tesla.
And the design is certainly more attractive.
But we're not allowed to have them.
And critically, I'm glad you brought this up
because the battery tech now
that's just being announced,
the sodium ion chemistry,
as well as the, I think BYD's focus on sulfide chemistry.
But we're talking about a million miles of usage.
I'm not in one charge, obviously,
but obviously thousands of chargers over time.
In other words, the car is gonna last,
I mean, the battery's gonna last longer than the car.
Oh yeah, the seats will wear out before the car does.
100%.
But those batteries will go into military drones.
They will go into military robots.
They will go into all kinds of other equipment.
And the US won't have that technology.
We are behind the curve in so many...
This is why you can hear frustration in my voice
because I'm an American.
I love America.
I want America to do well.
And I'm frustrated that we seem to be,
pardon my language,
just pissing away every opportunity to be a leader.
We're just sitting back with fraud and waste
and cover-ups and not being the America
that we were meant to be.
That's the way I see it.
I think you're 100% right.
I really do.
We're losing our leadership position.
We're behind the eight ball.
What happens when BRICS,
which is gonna continue to expand,
decides to come up with a unified currency?
Oh man, yeah.
And then they're buying oil
in whatever the new BRICS currency is gonna be.
We're done at that point.
We're done.
People will flee the dollar because we weaponized it.
So let me give out your podcast information here first.
So one of your podcasts is called Deep Focus.
And this is on Spotify.
I just wanna encourage everybody to follow Deep Focus
and it's John Kiriakou.
That's K-I-R-I-A-K-O-U.
Such a cool name you have there, by the way.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, very cool.
Thank you.
It means the son of Charles in Greek.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Oh, wow.
So I'll tell you a funny story.
My great-great-grand-grand.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me tell your other podcast.
Oh, sure, sure.
Apple.
It's called John Kiriakou's Dead Drop.
Dead Drop.
So that's very popular on the Apple podcast there too.
Be sure to check that out.
Sorry to interrupt.
Go ahead.
No, no, thank you.
Dead Drop has gone crazy.
Last week we were number eight in the world.
That's amazing.
This week we're number 11.
I don't know how that happened.
But anyway, my great-great-grandfather in the third quarter
of the 19th century was arrested for stealing a potato.
He was starving.
Really?
And he stole a potato.
And when he went to court, they said, what's your name?
And he said, Mark, Marcos.
Mark what?
Marcos to Kiriakou.
Mark the son of Charles.
And so they wrote Mark Kiriakou.
And we just never fixed it.
Really?
Wow.
OK, that's fascinating.
Well, I was wondering about your name.
I thought, I actually thought it might have been Greek,
but only because of the ending of the name.
Right.
The beginning, I couldn't quite make out the Kiri part.
Yeah.
Right.
But that's a son of Charles.
That's fascinating.
OK, this is Mike jumping in here.
That's the first half of the interview with John Kiriakiu.
And I thoroughly enjoyed this interview.
I'm gonna play the second half for you in part two,
which airs tomorrow.
So be sure to check that out.
And thank you for listening to today's interview.
I'm Mike Adams with brighttion.com.
Stock up on the long-term,
storable Ranger Bucket Set.
536 servings of clean organic superfoods
for your survival pantry.
Certified organic and lab tested for purity.
Order now at HealthRangerStore.com.